<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Let me get this right</title>
    <link>https://www.aidasalova.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Let me get this right</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.aidasalova.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>&#39;It sucks that...&#39; how to identify process improvement opportunities</title>
      <link>https://www.aidasalova.com/post/identify_improvements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aidasalova.com/post/identify_improvements/</guid>
      <description>Creating a smooth experience for end users, tapping into undiscovered needs and bringing efficiency into old-fashioned workflows is a multi-step process that involves an equal share of analytical skills, ingenuity, experience and intuition.
This task is all the more difficult because - as probably many of us discovered during these pandemic times - after a while we get used to everything. So we stop paying attention to annoying or simply unnecessary aspects of our life and take it as a given that the status quo is the only alternative possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Scrum in 500 Words</title>
      <link>https://www.aidasalova.com/post/scrum_intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aidasalova.com/post/scrum_intro/</guid>
      <description>Scrum is an agile framework aimed to address complex problems and especially widely used in software development, although Scrum can really be applied in any sphere. And while Scrum is famously difficult to master, this short article is aimed to cover the very basics of what it represents.
The heart of Scrum is a transparent collaboration of a self-managing small group of people who hold specific accountabilities within this group, continuously inspect the environment and adapt to it to deliver the maximum value in an iterative fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
