<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Let me get this right</title>
    <link>https://www.aidasalova.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Let me get this right</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.aidasalova.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Facing the Abyss</title>
      <link>https://www.aidasalova.com/post/facing_the_abyss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aidasalova.com/post/facing_the_abyss/</guid>
      <description>I took on skiing as an adult having never skied until then. The cold crisp air of the mountain, the snow sparkling under the sun, the silence is what attracted me.
Any person starting to ski in their mid-life knows the feeling of admiration and jealousy towards kids who fearlessly zip forward on the steep routes. Being adults, we carry too much baggage - anxiety, fear, ego, what-ifs…
One of the things that is particularly difficult for someone new to skiing is to lean towards the abyss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to give structure to creative thinking</title>
      <link>https://www.aidasalova.com/post/creative_thinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aidasalova.com/post/creative_thinking/</guid>
      <description>The word “creativity” often brings to mind a sunlit studio where an artist in a black turtleneck throws paint on a canvas. Or a designer trying a dress made of plastic bags and violet petals on a model. Or a composer scribbling notes on a lined paper while whistling a tune. In other words, something that has nothing to do with our daily lives.
What my recent course on Creativity within the MBA program asserted from the beginning is that this assumption is totally wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why new (good) stuff fails: Prospect theory in 500 words</title>
      <link>https://www.aidasalova.com/post/prospect_theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aidasalova.com/post/prospect_theory/</guid>
      <description>It can be frustrating sometimes. Designing a new feature with the expectation that excited users will thank you for the great new stuff … only to discover that users couldn’t care less about it.
The prospect theory developed by Daniel Kahneman and Amos Tversky might have a good explanation for this. According to this theory, when faced with a choice (e.g. use a new feature, buy a new product) people think in terms of their gains and losses with respect to a reference point rather than in absolute terms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;It sucks that...&#39; how to identify process improvement opportunities</title>
      <link>https://www.aidasalova.com/post/identify_improvements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aidasalova.com/post/identify_improvements/</guid>
      <description>Creating a smooth experience for end users, tapping into undiscovered needs and bringing efficiency into old-fashioned workflows is a multi-step process that involves an equal share of analytical skills, ingenuity, experience and intuition.
This task is all the more difficult because - as probably many of us discovered during these pandemic times - after a while we get used to everything. So we stop paying attention to annoying or simply unnecessary aspects of our life and take it as a given that the status quo is the only alternative possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Scrum in 500 Words</title>
      <link>https://www.aidasalova.com/post/scrum_intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aidasalova.com/post/scrum_intro/</guid>
      <description>Scrum is an agile framework aimed to address complex problems and especially widely used in software development, although Scrum can really be applied in any sphere. And while Scrum is famously difficult to master, this short article is aimed to cover the very basics of what it represents.
The heart of Scrum is a transparent collaboration of a self-managing small group of people who hold specific accountabilities within this group, continuously inspect the environment and adapt to it to deliver the maximum value in an iterative fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
