<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>500 words on Let me get this right</title>
    <link>https://www.aidasalova.com/tags/500-words/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 500 words on Let me get this right</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.aidasalova.com/tags/500-words/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why new (good) stuff fails: Prospect theory in 500 words</title>
      <link>https://www.aidasalova.com/post/prospect_theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aidasalova.com/post/prospect_theory/</guid>
      <description>It can be frustrating sometimes. Designing a new feature with the expectation that excited users will thank you for the great new stuff … only to discover that users couldn’t care less about it.
The prospect theory developed by Daniel Kahneman and Amos Tversky might have a good explanation for this. According to this theory, when faced with a choice (e.g. use a new feature, buy a new product) people think in terms of their gains and losses with respect to a reference point rather than in absolute terms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Scrum in 500 Words</title>
      <link>https://www.aidasalova.com/post/scrum_intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aidasalova.com/post/scrum_intro/</guid>
      <description>Scrum is an agile framework aimed to address complex problems and especially widely used in software development, although Scrum can really be applied in any sphere. And while Scrum is famously difficult to master, this short article is aimed to cover the very basics of what it represents.
The heart of Scrum is a transparent collaboration of a self-managing small group of people who hold specific accountabilities within this group, continuously inspect the environment and adapt to it to deliver the maximum value in an iterative fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
